Guide to the Henry Leveke Kamphoefner Papers, 1924 - 1990 MC 00198
Special Collections Research Center
- Project Specifications, 1932-1947
  - Residence, Norman, Oklahoma, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Classroom Building, University of Oklahoma, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Oklahoma Solar House, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Additions, 1937-1980, undated; 3 boxes
  This series comprises some late accessions to the collection. These materials have been arranged in three subseries: Photographs, Artifacts and Memorabilia, and Publications. Travel snapshots of landscapes and buildings from the American West and several national parks make up the bulk of the photographs subseries. The artifacts and memorabilia subseries includes personal effects belonging to Henry L. Kamphoefner and his wife, Mabel C. Kamphoefner. The publications subseries contains only one item: a copy of the book "Your Solar House" (1947), to which Henry L. Kamphoefner contributed.
  - Photographs, 1945, undated
    - Professional, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Travel, undated
      - Landscapes, undated
        - Columbia River Highway, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
        - Animals, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
        - Mt. Rushmore, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 76, Folder 10, Folder 7, Folder 6, Folder 9, Folder 8, Folder 5)
      - Buildings, undated
        - Statues, undated (Box 76, Folder 11)
        - Dams, undated (Box 76, Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 76, Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21, Box 77, Folder 1, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 2)
      - People, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - 1 5/8 x 2 prints, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - 5 x 1 prints, undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Family, undated
      - People, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Homes, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Pets, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Envelope, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Artifacts and Memorabilia, 1937-1980, undated
    - The Marriage Service, Booklet with Certificate, 1937 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings and Articles, 1944-1951
      - Residence in Norman, Oklahoma, 1944-1945 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Residence in Raleigh, North Carolina, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Passport, Henry L. Kamphoefner, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Sports Medals, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Mabel C. Kamphoefner, 1946, undated
      - Birth Certificate [copy], 1946 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Books Read Ledger, undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1947
    - "Your Solar House," Book, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 8)